<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods:mods xmlns:mods="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">  
          <mods:titleInfo> 
            <mods:title>Gamer, Carlton</mods:title> 
          </mods:titleInfo>  
          <mods:name> 
            <mods:namePart>Finley, Judith Reid, 1936-</mods:namePart>  
            <mods:role> 
              <mods:roleTerm authority="marcrelator" type="text">creator</mods:roleTerm> 
            </mods:role> 
          </mods:name>  
          <mods:typeOfResource>mixed material</mods:typeOfResource>  
          <mods:originInfo> 
            <mods:place> 
              <mods:placeTerm>Colorado Springs, Colorado</mods:placeTerm> 
            </mods:place>  
            <mods:publisher>Colorado College</mods:publisher>  
            <mods:dateCreated keyDate="yes">1995-03-08</mods:dateCreated>  
            <mods:dateCaptured>2010-05-21</mods:dateCaptured> 
          </mods:originInfo>  
          <mods:language type="text"> 
            <mods:languageTerm>eng</mods:languageTerm> 
          </mods:language>  
          <mods:physicalDescription> 
            <mods:extent></mods:extent>  
            <mods:digitalOrigin>reformatted digital</mods:digitalOrigin> 
          </mods:physicalDescription>  
          <mods:abstract>A noted composer and music theorist, Professor Carlton Gamer received his Bachelors in Music from Northwestern University in 1950, and his Masters from Boston University in 1951. He came to Colorado College first in 1953 as an accompanist for the dance program. From 1954 through 1960, he was a full-time instructor in the music department. He became assistant professor in 1960; associate professor in 1966; and served as a full professor from 1974 until his retirement in 1994. Besides his talents as a composer and teacher of music, Professor Gamer also has had a great interest in Asian culture and philosophy and mathematical thought. As a conscientious objector, Professor Gamer counseled many young men about the draft.</mods:abstract>  
          <mods:targetAudience></mods:targetAudience>  
          <mods:note type="venue"></mods:note>  
          <mods:note type="admin">Digitized from the original Special Collections Audio tape R76. This interview is part of a larger collection totaling 89 individuals. Interview transcripts converted to PDF/A from Microsoft Word. Other file materials, biographical data sheets, indexes, legal releases scanned from originals and converted to text searchable PDF/A using Fujitsu 4150 scanner and Scandallpro software version 1.5. Scanned at 400 dpi. Photos scanned at 500 dpi and saved as jpeg. There are 131 preservation wave files (44.1 kHz, 16-bit) and 131 delivery mp3 files (128 kbps) in the set. Each file represents up to an hour of material, equivalent to one side of a reel-to-reel tape or both sides of a cassette tape. The 262 files are now located on both of two hard drives in Special Collections, the master drive (A1) formatted for Mac and a backup drive (B1) formatted for PC. (.wav preservation masters created by Tom Sanny using Final Cut Pro. Analog tapes digitized as QuickTime 44k16b .mov files. Dead air edited out and sound levels adjusted ; .wav files exported using FCP QuickTime Conversion tool ; .mp3 files created from .wav files using Switch.) All files are monaural.</mods:note>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:topic>Oral history</mods:topic> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:topic>Universities and colleges</mods:topic> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:topic>Faculty</mods:topic> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:topic>Music</mods:topic> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:name type="corporate"> 
              <mods:namePart>Colorado College</mods:namePart> 
            </mods:name> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:name type="corporate"> 
              <mods:namePart>Colorado College. Dept. of Music</mods:namePart> 
            </mods:name> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:name type="personal"> 
              <mods:namePart>Gamer, Carlton</mods:namePart> 
            </mods:name> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:temporal>1950-1959</mods:temporal> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:temporal>1960-1969</mods:temporal> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:temporal>1970-1979</mods:temporal> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:temporal>1980-1989</mods:temporal> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:temporal>1990-1999</mods:temporal> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:geographic>Colorado</mods:geographic> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:geographic>Colorado Springs (Colo.)</mods:geographic> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:genre>Personal narratives</mods:genre> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:subject> 
            <mods:genre>Audio recording</mods:genre> 
          </mods:subject>  
          <mods:relatedItem type="series">
            <mods:titleInfo>
               <mods:title>Colorado College Oral History Collection</mods:title> 
            </mods:titleInfo> 
          </mods:relatedItem>  
          <mods:location> 
            <mods:url usage="primary display">http://hdl.handle.net/10176/coccc:3049</mods:url> 
          </mods:location>  
          <mods:accessCondition type="useAndReproduction">Portions of this interview may only be used for educational or scholarly purposes. All rights in the manuscript and recording, including the right to publish, are reserved to the Colorado College Tutt Library. PERMISSION TO PUBLISH IN ANY FORMAT MUST BE REQUESTED from Special Collections, Colorado College Tutt Library.</mods:accessCondition>  
          <mods:recordInfo> 
            <mods:languageOfCataloging> 
                <mods:languageTerm type="text" authority="iso639-2b">English</mods:languageTerm>
                <mods:languageTerm type="code" authority="iso639-2b">eng</mods:languageTerm>
            </mods:languageOfCataloging> 
          </mods:recordInfo> 
        </mods:mods>
